Today we are going to learn about corporal punishment.
Definition: Corporal punishment is physical punishment.
It uses all types of physical punishment including pinching, spanking, pulling, slapping,
twisting and hitting with an object. It also may include forcing someone to consume
an unpleasant substance, for example soup, hot sauce or hot pepper.
The basics. Understand the rules. Whenever your submissive does something wrong,
you punish him to teach him a lesson but remember to provide encouragement and reward
for those things that he does right. You need to make sure your client understands
the rules before carrying out your session.
Fair punishment. The punishment should be fair.
Your client, for example, may have a bad attitude, break a rule or something similar.
Whatever discipline you choose should be more or less equal to the seriousness of
the rule break. Very minor mistakes will be punishable by a minor punishment.
For example, a gentle spank. Save your harder BDSM punishments for more serious rule
breaks or repeated rule breaks. Stay calm.
Never give out a punishment in anger. Take a deep breath, calm down and then think
of what punishment is fair for your client.
If you act in anger you are likely to give out a harsher punishment when it isn't
needed. If you give out punishment while you're angry you could potentially hit your
sub. Know their limits. Know your sub's limits.
The punishments you hand to your submissive should be practical and able to complete.
You never want to give your sub something that is too harsh.
For example, you can't expect someone with an injury to hold themselves in a place
for a prolonged period of time which could potentially make the injury worse.
Please avoid punishments that could be dangerous like cutting off their circulation.
Your submissive might be so fixed on pleasing you that he goes beyond his limits
performing potentially dangerous tasks. You need to make sure you keep this a safe
place for yourself and your client. Pay close attention to your clients when you're
making them perform more serious punishments.
No surprises. Having your client perform surprise punishments on himself is not something
we recommend. We want your client to trust you and part of that trust is that you
hand out fair punishments. If you hand out a surprise punishment to your client, he
will not know what the punishment is for.
He will then begin to feel very unsafe in your hands.
He may never want to carry out a session like this again.
We have added some ideas to get you started.
Now would be a good idea to pause the video to take a photo or take down your own
notes to use in the future. Sometimes you may run out of ideas, so on these
occasions you can have your submissives come up with their own punishments.
Not all BDSM punishments have to come from you.
You can get your client to come up with his own tasks.
You can have your sub come up with a list of punishments for each offence.
You can then pick and decide what punishment from the list he will endure.
Be careful of a cheeky submissive who might try and get away with an easier punishment
but only suggesting ones he doesn't mind doing.
If this happens, I would recommend giving him a harsh punishment for trying to pull
the wool over your eyes. I hope this has been beneficial for you and you've
got a lot of new ideas to explore with your clients.
There are a lot of different punishments on there for you to try, so as I explained
in a previous video, I'd recommend printing off the list or just writing it down on
a notepad you can keep with you. That way when your client comes into the chat you've
got a long list of punishments to try with him.
Also, like I said in the humiliation video, always start off a little bit
easier, not so hard with the punishments, and you know not a really extravagant one.
Ease him into it and see what he's comfortable with, and then you can always go a
little bit further and a little bit further, but always make sure that it's a safe
space for your client. If he doesn't feel safe, he will likely go to somebody else.
So yeah, good luck girlies and see you on the next video.